Guide to the Washington State University Audio/Video Materials 1930-2005
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- SERIES 6: WSU-PRODUCED NEWS STORIES AND OTHER MATERIALS.
  - "Celebration of Graduate Excellence." KWSU Media. Video: VHS. 60' tape, 2002 April 16 (Box 21, Item 6)
  - Allen Foundation "Thank you." KWSU Media. Video: VHS. 30' tape, 2002-04 (Box 21, Item 7)
  - Discoveries and Breakthroughs. KWSU Media. Video: Betacam. 30 min., 2002 July 30 (Box 21, Item 8)
  - Future Teachers of Color. KWSU Media. Video: VHS, 2002 (Box 21, Item 9)
  - WSU Foundation 25th Anniversary. Includes sheet with V. Lane Rawlins production release. Video: VHS, 2004-10 (Box 21, Item 10)
  - Mentoring to Veterans Luncheon. Video: VHS. 57 min., 2005 August 30 (Box 21, Item 11)
  - CCM Access "Access Through Distance Education." Video: VHS, undated (Box 21, Item 12)
  - ASWSU Bulletin- Ben Dow on use of WSU logo. Note from Doug Baker to Mary Gresch about Dow's desire to put announcements on campus TVs in classrooms btwn classes. Tape is an example of what would play. Video: VHS. 120' tape, undated (Box 21, Item 13)
  - College of Agriculture and Home Economics. Video: VHS, undated (Box 21, Item 14)
  - Conflict or Consensus? The Lake Roosevelt Forum. Handwritten note on tape label: Rec 6-3-94 from Kelsey Gray. Video: VHS. 14:36, 1994 (Box 21, Item 15)
  - Cougar Pause. "The Washington Wine Industry: A New Frontier" KWSU and KTNW. Video: VHS. 29:38, undated (Box 21, Item 16)
  - Critical Thinking. Video: VHS, undated (Box 21, Item 17)
  - WSU News and Info: Fall Registration. Video: VHS. 0:30, undated (Box 21, Item 18)
  - WSU College of Education. Future Teachers of Color Program. Video: VHS, undated (Box 21, Item 19)
  - Jenny Godjali/Maranda/Devi Mandrawa. Video: VHS, undated (Box 21, Item 20)
  - Grand Old Lady: Davenport Hotel. Video: VHS, undated (Box 21, Item 21)
  - WSU Learning Center Demonstration. Video: VHS. 5 min., undated (Box 21, Item 22)
  - Museums. Video: VHS, undated (Box 21, Item 23)
  - Grace Ogoshi-Mayer. EDP student. Video: VHS, undated (Box 21, Item 24)
  - P1000 Starlight #4267/M1. Label from Battelle, Pacific Northwest Laboratories, Chief Scientists James J. Thomas. Video: VHS. 7:38, undated (Box 21, Item 25)
  - Sun-Im Shin, Copsy511, Counseling Tape. Video: VHS. 120 min tape, undated (Box 21, Item 26)
  - Tacoma Rocketts. FTOC package. Video: VHS. 1:32, undated (Box 21, Item 27)
  - Tape 1 - CTLT Student Computing Services. Video: S-VHS, undated (Box 21, Item 28)
  - Tape 2 - General Education. Video: S-VHS, undated (Box 21, Item 29)
  - Tape 3 - CUE. Writing Center, Writing Assessment, Some b-roll. Video: S-VHS, undated (Box 21, Item 30)
  - Discarded on 6/9/2015. MOE. (Box 21, Item 31)
  - WSU - Cable 8 Productions Demo DVD. Neal Robison, Stephen Thorpe Producer. Digital Video: DVD, 2004-04 (Box 21, Item 32)
  - Albrook lab - Vancouver Lake hydrologic study. Film: 16mm - silent, color, undated (Box 21, Item 33)
  - Women's rodeo. Film: 16mm - silent, color, 1960s-1970s (Box 21, Item 34)
  - "Recorded from KWSC radio broadcast." Audio: 1/4" open reel audio tape, 1967 December 04 (Box 22, Item 1)
  - "Audition." 4 anncrs, 1 cut each. Audio: 1/4" open reel audio tape. 600' tape, undated (Box 22, Item 2)
  - "Original Cuts" 4 anncrs, 6 cuts each. Note with box reads "7 spots tp be transferred - 6 voiced by Gay, 1 by Ruddy, ends with one on foundation." Audio: 1/4" open reel audio tape. 600' tape, undated (Box 22, Item 3)
  - Dick Fry #1 on box but NOT Dick Fry. Speaker referring to 19 yr old vote that was a State of WA idea in 1970. Governor (Dan Evans) created a Commission for Youth Involvement and this male speaker refers to the Report of that Comission. Refers also to 5 da (Box 22, Item 4)
  - Unlabeled tape: "Educational television is?" Audio: 1/4" open reel audio tape, undated (Box 22, Item 5)
  - Unlabeled tape: possibly WSU promotional commercials. Audio: 1/4" open reel audio tape, undated (Box 22, Item 6)
  - Unlabeled tape: "Washington State University is closing the page on its first century." Audio: 1/4" open reel audio tape, 1990 ca. (Box 22, Item 7)
  - Unlabeled tape: Commercials for WSU college scholarship funds. Audio: 1/4" open reel audio tape, undated (Box 22, Item 8)
  - WSU Spokane. A focus group discussing WSU Spokane and its role in the community. Audio: 1/8" tape Standard Audio cassette, undated (Box 22, Item 9)
  - "Grievances"?. Audio: 1/8" tape Standard Audio cassette. 60' tape, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Item 10)
  - Roundtable 8: Mitochondrial DNA. Audio: 1/8" tape Standard Audio cassette. 93' tape, undated (Box 22, Item 11)
  - WSU Radio Newsline. AV Cassette by A. Audio: 1/8" tape Standard Audio cassette. 30' tape, undated (Box 22, Item 12)
- SERIES 7: NEWS FOOTAGE AND PRODUCED PROGRAMS FROM NON_CAMPUS SOURCES.
  - CBS News: Person to Person with Janet Murrow. Video: 3/4" U-matic. approx. 25 min., 1954 December 21 (dubbed 1993-03-24) (Box 23, Item 1)
  - KING TV 5. "Washington 2000." Video: VHS. 120 min tape, 1985 September 16 (Box 23, Item 2)
  - Butch the Cougar, "12 for the Road." KOMO TV (Seattle). Video: VHS, 1992 November 12 (Box 23, Item 3)
  - Information coordinator for branch campus. Nancy Hilliard. KREM news cast. Video: VHS, 1992 December 10 (Box 23, Item 4)
  - 1993 Governor's Inaugural Ball. Spiritborne Productions (Olympia). Video: VHS. 120' tape, 1993 January 13 (Box 23, Item 5)
  - Northwest Black Pioneers. The Bon Marche for the ongoing celebration of Northwest Black History. Video: VHS. 30' tape, 1994-02 (Box 23, Item 6)
  - Presentation of 1994 Black Engineer of the Year Award in Baltimore to WSU Regent and PhD graduate William R. Wiley of Battelle and PNNL. Typescript in case is media release about Wiley winning award. Video: VHS. 6:28, 1994 February 12 (Box 23, Item 7)
  - NBC Nightly News (Generation X Story) Sen: Murray. Video: VHS. TRT 0:04:00, 1994 June 13 (Box 23, Item 8)
  - "When America Trembled" CBS-TV Murrow/McCarthy. Video: VHS. 120' tape, 1994 June 15 (Box 23, Item 9)
  - Promotional materials about "When America Trembled" Paper., undated (Box 23, Item 0)
  - Governor Gary Locke's visti to the Wenatchee Valley College WHETS Center. Inside tape case is a manuscript note about who spoke on the tape. Note taped to case refers to not having clearances for student images and voices on the tape. Video: VHS. 60' tape, 1997 February 21 (Box 23, Item 10)
  - The Lost Art of Learning. Tempo IV News Monitoring Service (Kirkland, WA) - News 10:00 pm KIRO. Video: VHS, 1997 February 24 (Box 23, Item 11)
  - KIRO News - Pet MRI. Video: VHS. A few minutes, 1999 February 17 (Box 23, Item 12)
  - True Colors "Future of Higher Ed" KOMO-4. Video: VHS. 30' tape, 1999 March 30 (Box 23, Item 13)
  - KOMO TV Apple Cup newscast. Sam Smith and Kathi Goertzen. Also GM food controversy. Video: VHS, 1999 November 19 (Box 23, Item 14)
  - Dr. Shira Broschat "Health Watch" KOMO-TV (Kathi Goertzen, anchor) Faculty Fireside. Video: VHS. 120' tape, 2000 October 13 (Box 23, Item 15)
  - The Generous Rich BBC World. Sunday Nov. 5, 2000. Video: VHS. 120' tape, 2000 November 05 (Box 23, Item 16)
  - CoGen - KREM Story (on case). Tape label is "Producing Power" KREM 6 pm Newscase. Video: VHS, 2001 January 23 (Box 23, Item 17)
  - KLEW-TV (Lewiston) Newscast covering memorial service for three WSU students killed in traffic accident. Video: VHS. 120' tape, 2001 June 14 (Box 23, Item 18)
  - Seafair Parade 1. WSU Band and Butch in Staging Area 2. UW in Parade 3. WSU in Parade. Video: VHS, 2001 July 29 (Box 23, Item 19)
  - ABC 20/20 CEO of Kanter-Fitzgerald. Video: VHS, 2001 October 10 (Box 23, Item 20)
  - KREM 5 and 11 pm KXLY 5 and 11 pm Newscases Foreign Students Leaving WSU. Video: VHS, 37154 (Box 23, Item 21)
  - KHQ Cancer Consortium News Conference. Video: VHS, 2001 November 02 (Box 23, Item 22)
  - CBS 60 Minutes II AVID. Video: VHS, 2002 January 30 (Box 23, Item 23)
  - KREM/KXLY Attic Coverage. Video: VHS, 2002 October 22 (Box 23, Item 24)
  - KREM 6 pm and KXLY 11 pm Newscasts Pullman Brawl. Video: VHS, 2002 October 22 (Box 23, Item 25)
  - Today Show segment on Dave 'Blue' Waterstraat - 60 year old fraternity member. Video: VHS, undated (Box 23, Item 26)
  - America's Most Wined. ZD TV on tape. Video: VHS, undated (Box 23, Item 27)
  - KOMO - Apple Cup Feature/Gertzen Award/GM Foods. Video: VHS. A few minutes, undated (Box 23, Item 28)
  - Connects 515 College Presidents. Video: VHS, undated (Box 23, Item 29)
  - Crossfire - Dogs. Video: VHS, undated (Box 23, Item 30)
  - Collin on KING TV "Falling Debris." Video: VHS, 19uu May 03 (Box 23, Item 31)
  - KREM 2 News Foley Challenge. Note indicates was recording from 5 and 6 pm KREM News for "Foley Challenge to Kennedy". Video: VHS. 120 min tape, undated (Box 23, Item 32)
  - CBS 60 Mininutes and 48 Hours. Video: VHS, undated (Box 23, Item 33)
  - KPBX radio interview. Francis Ho:Black and White Photographs: "Dualities". Audio: 1/8" tape Standard Audio cassette, 34225 (Box 23, Item 34)
  - KPBX "Inland Journal" program that seems to be devoted to medical research in Spokane. Doug Nadvornick hosts program and Mark Garrison (?) of WSU Spokane is 1 of people interviewed. Audio: 1/8" tape Standard Audio cassette, undated (Box 23, Item 35)
  - Cougar Pride Days 30 sec. radio spot. KQQQ/KHTR Radio Pullman, Voice talent: Brock and Bryn Howell. Audio: 1/8" tape Standard Audio cassette. 30 sec., 2002 March 04 (Box 23, Item 36)